{
    "subject": "resource/Newton_Running",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:Shoe_brands",
    "human_readable": "The subject of Newton Running is Shoe brands.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9700068831443787,
            "question": "Is Newton Running a popular brand of footwear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7930388450622559,
            "question": "How does Newton Running compare to other shoe brands?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7190672159194946,
            "question": "Give an example of a brand that makes running shoes."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7106019258499146,
            "question": "Are there different types of running shoes made by Newton Running?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.699129045009613,
            "question": "Who might be interested in purchasing Newton Running shoes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6963361501693726,
            "question": "What type of product is Newton Running?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6734552979469299,
            "question": "What are some features that distinguish Newton Running shoes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6195909380912781,
            "question": "Where can you buy Newton Running shoes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5942083597183228,
            "question": "What are the benefits of wearing Newton Running shoes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48881903290748596,
            "question": "What is the target market for Newton Running?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The subject of Newton Running is Shoe brands.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4696_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are the benefits of wearing Newton Running shoes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4696_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where can you buy Newton Running shoes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4696_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some features that distinguish Newton Running shoes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4696_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4696_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4696_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4696_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4696_115.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4696_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4696_134.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4696_155.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4696_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4696_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4696_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that the subject of Newton Running is Shoe brands. The text describes Newton Running as a brand that specializes in designing and manufacturing running shoes, and mentions that it is a leading Natural Running footwear brand."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that the subject of \"Newton Running\" is indeed related to shoe brands, specifically running shoes. The texts describe the brand's focus on natural running form and provide details about their product offerings and technology."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}